https://www.reef.com/privacy-policy.html

<>
2 FOR 20% OFF *SELECT SANDALS ONLY.
All Boys Sandals
Littles (2-4 Yrs)
Kids (5-8 Yrs)
Girls Sandals
All Girls Sandals
Littles (2-4 Yrs)
Kids (5-8 Yrs)
View All
Get jolly for this holiday season! Shop Reef Holiday Gift Guide. Find comfy and cozy gifts for everyone on your list, including yourself. Free shipping & returns.
The Homebody
Life of the Party
The Stylish One
The Practical One
Ballin' on a Budget
About Reef
https://www.reef.com/about-us.html
View All
INTRODUCTION
REEF ("REEF” or “we, us or our”)  has developed this Online Privacy Policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to inform you of our commitment to privacy and to describe our policies for the collection, use, and disclosure of personal information that may be collected by REEF when you visit our websites or use certain services on www.Reef.com. By accessing or using this website or other REEF services, you consent to our Privacy Policy. REEF may modify this Privacy Policy at any time effective upon its posting. Your continued use of our website or services constitutes your acceptance to this Privacy Policy and any updates. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into, and is subject to, the Terms of Use.
REEF is not responsible for the privacy practices of any company to which our Websites might link. For access to the privacy policies of those sites, please refer to the policies provided by those sites at their home pages.
INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM YOU
REEF will collect information that you give us or permit us to access. This information may include, without limitation, your name, email, physical address, telephone number, gender, birth date, contact lists, social media information and profile, online activity and performance information, and credit card information when necessary.
WHAT KIND OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?
PERSONAL INFORMATION
REEF collects personal information when you establish a user profile or account purchase merchandise from the Website, register for contests and promotions, submit requests to REEF customer service, respond to communications from REEF and for other services that require registration or subscription. The personal information collected by or on behalf of REEF may include, without limitation, your name, e-mail address, birth date, address, zip code, telephone number credit or debit card information, and other related information, usage and other demographic information, as applicable. In addition, personal information is collected in certain portions of the Websites in which visitors provide such information along with content submissions, community postings (e.g., chat or bulletin boards), suggestions, surveys, polls or voting. Please note that when you make a purchase from any of the Websites, we may need to contact you via phone, postal mail or e-mail if we have questions regarding your order. If you have opted-in to receive communications, including e-mails and/or SMS messages from REEF, we will use your information to customize advertising and content we present to you, and to send you information and materials, including, without limitation, via e-mail or SMS messages about products, offers and news that we think could interest you. This information may relate to products, offers and news of REEF or its licensees or carefully selected commercial partners. REEF may also collect personal information from you about a third party to carry out services relating to you or that third party at your request (e.g. delivering e-post card or shipping gift to a third party).
NON-PERSONAL AND AGGREGATE DATA
When you visit our Websites, we may collect "click stream" data (IP address, server address, domain name, browser information, and other non-personally identifiable information regarding your visit. This information may be combined with information you have provided to us (for instance by registering), which will enable us to analyze and better customize your visits. Like many websites, we may collect information regarding website usage by using cookies and tracking technologies. We may use information gathered from the cookies and tracking technologies to analyze and understand how the Websites are used and to enhance your visits to the Websites. For example, we may use cookies and tracking technologies to: (i) customize account pages for you; (ii) track user visits and account set-ups; (iii) determine what set-ups are most frequently requested; and (iv) provide for a "remember me" function to save your user name and password so you do not have to provide it each time you visit the Websites. You can find more information on how we use cookies in the section titled "Use of Cookies." We may also use a third-party service provider to help us optimize the products and services we offer through the Websites. That third party may place web beacons or data tags on the Websites and/or a cookie on your computer to facilitate collection of information on use of the Websites each time you visit the Website ("Session Data"). If, at any time you do not wish to allow your Session Data to be aggregated and analyzed by that third party, click here and utilize the opt-out mechanism. This opt-out mechanism is only applicable to cookies placed on your computer by that third party.
USE OF COOKIES
We use "cookies," like other websites, which are files stored on your computer’s hard drive by your browser to identify account holders. Cookies allow us to follow your activity on the Websites and help us to understand your shopping preferences, improve your website experience and remember user information such as your user name and password. You can turn off all cookies if you prefer not to receive them. You can also have your computer warn you whenever cookies are being used. For both options you must adjust your browser settings. Please note than when you set your computer to reject cookies, the settings may limit the functionality of the website you visit and it is possible that you will not have access to some of the features on the website.
USE OF YOUR INFORMATION
Except for the purposes set forth below and otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, REEF will not share, sell, trade or otherwise transfer personal information. We will use your personal information to provide products and services to you and to perform, without limitation, the following:
Business Uses
REEF uses the personal information that you provide to: (i) establish user profiles and accounts and store user preferences; (ii) administer and fulfill contests, promotions, surveys or other site features (for instance to deliver a prize you may have won in a contest); (iii) provide you with the products or services that you have ordered or requested; (iv) process and ship orders; (v) send order and shipping confirmations; (vi) provide customer service; (vii) process returns or exchanges; (viii) protect you, and us, against error and fraud; (ix) keep records of returns and exchanges; and (x) investigate or enforce legal rights and obligations. Information collected on or through the Websites may be shared or transferred to third parties who perform services for us or with whom we contract for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may use third parties to host our Websites, assist in designing and operating the Websites or certain features, perform services (e.g., prize fulfillment), print or send communications on behalf of REEF, authorize and process payments, process and administer gift cards, provide customer service and help us analyze data. These third-party providers are required to employ a comparable level of protection for personal consumer information. Further, REEF only provides these third-party providers with the information necessary to perform their designated functions and/or services. You may be asked on certain areas of our Websites whether you wish to receive information from third parties and, upon your consent, REEF and/or those third parties may use the personal information you provide to contact you consistent with the consent that you provided as permitted by applicable law.
Non-Personal Information
We may use non-personal information to analyze visits to the Websites and learn about the interests of our visitors in aggregate and to better understand your interests and needs, so we can improve our products and services and deliver to you the type of content, features and promotions in which you are most interested. We may share non-personal, aggregate data with our marketing partners or other third parties for research and marketing purposes. On occasion, we may combine information that we received on or through the Websites with information obtained from other sources and outside records to enable us to update and correct the information contained in our database.
Who Manages Your Information
The information collected is managed and controlled by REEF or by third party service providers that are required to maintain the security and confidentiality standards described in this Privacy Policy on behalf of REEF. The servers that make the Websites available and that store the information collected by REEF are located in the United States of America. Accordingly, even if you do not live in the United States, you consent to have your personal information transferred, processed, and stored in the United States and allow REEF to use and collect your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
Protection of Your Information
Like other companies, we cannot guarantee 100%, that the security or confidentiality of the information that you have provided to us. However, REEF takes administrative, technical and physical precautions to safeguard your personal information against loss, theft, and misuse, as well as unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction and we require our third-party service providers to do the same.
SECURITY POLICY
Keeping your personal information confidential and secure is important to us. In order to protect the payment information you provide to us, including your credit card number, expiration date, security code, and billing address, we use 2048-bit Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology. SSL technology encrypts your information so that it cannot be recognized or decoded in cyberspace.
Your computer will begin operating in secure mode once you enter our checkout page. You can confirm that SSL is active by looking in the lower left hand corner of your browser, where you will see either a closed lock or an unbroken key (depending on your browser type). Additionally, the URL line of your browser will change from "http" to "https" when the SSL technology is operating. REEF’s policy regarding the security of credit card information can be found by clicking on the “Security Policy” link on the left hand side of this page. The Security Policy is incorporated into this Privacy Policy by reference.
CHILDREN'S PRIVACY
REEF does not knowingly collect or solicit the personal information from children under 13 years of age.
Residents of California
In accordance with California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of California may submit a once-a-year request for information concerning our disclosures of their personal information to third parties for direct marketing purposes, if any. Please send a written request, including your name and address, to:
5935 Darwin Court
Carlsbad, CA 92008
Attention: REEF PRIVACY POLICY, Legal Department
By Email: consumercare@reef.com
Please include "Request for California Privacy" in the letter subject line. Within thirty (30) days of receiving your request, we will send you a list of the categories of personal information disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes during the immediately preceding calendar year. We will also provide you with the names and addresses of these third parties. REEF reserves the right to not respond to requests sent more than once in a calendar year. Our disclosures are limited to the information covered by the law.
RIGHT OF ACCESS
You have a right to access your personal information. You may exercise this right by visiting the "My Account" section of the website. From this link, you can view, modify or delete your personal information from our database. Please note that REEF reserves the right to retain personal information relating to you reasonably necessary to document its business activities or as needed for required disclosures.
YOUR CHOICES
You are not required to provide us with your personal information. Your provision of any personal information to us on or through our Websites or by other means must be voluntary and with your consent to the uses described in this Privacy Policy. In some cases, only persons who provide the requested personal information will be able to order products and services or otherwise participate in the Websites' activities and offerings. If you would like to be on our e-mail list, you will be provided with the opportunity to designate your preference on the Website. You will also have the opportunity to "opt-in" to join our mailing list. If you provide your mobile phone number and would like to receive text messages and/or SMS messages from us, you will have the opportunity to "opt-in" to receive those communications.
OPT-OUTS
You may opt-out of receiving future e-mail communications by clicking on an "unsubscribe" hyperlink contained in promotional, commercial e-mails we send to you. Please note that unless you cancel your registration, you will not be able to opt-out of receiving all types of communications, such as service announcements and administrative messages, as these types of communications are a necessary part of your account and use of the Websites.
CANCELLATION OF REGISTRATION
You may cancel your user registration at any time, and you can choose to opt-out of receiving any future e-mails and/or SMS messages from REEF. Please note that modifications of the status of personal information will not stop e-mails and/or SMS messages (i) generated before REEF can accomplish the modification of the status of personal information or (ii) from third parties with whom REEF may have already shared that personal information consistent with this Privacy Policy.
If you have any questions about the Privacy Policy please visit the Contact Us section of our web site, or call us at 1-844-500-7333 or write to us at:
5935 Darwin Court
Carlsbad, CA 92008
Attention: REEF PRIVACY POLICY, Legal Department
By Email: consumercare@reef.com
